Guide to the
Stanford University. Libraries.
- George Forsythe Papers, 1938-1972; Series 1
  - Matrix Conference - Wayne State University, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Matrix Eigenvalues - Jacobi (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Matrix Eigenvalues - Jacobi - Rosser (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Matrix Eigenvalues (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Matrix Eingenvalues (cont) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Matrix Eigenvalues OR (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Matrix Eigenvalues - Computer (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Matrix Examples (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Matrix Fundamentals (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Matrix - Jacobi - Hansen (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Matrix - Jacobi - Henrici (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Matrix Matters - RW (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Matrix - Salkoff (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Matrix - Scaling (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Matrix - Singular Values (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Matrix Inversion: Gradient (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Max-Min (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Max-Min Opt-S-Gradient (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - McCraith (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - McCready (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Mechanical Translation (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Medical School (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Merenbach (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Meteorology Courses (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Meteorology Dynamics (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Meteorology - Numerical Work (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Meteorology - Research (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Meteorology - Winds (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous - Pure Math (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Mitchell, Harry (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Modular Arithmetic (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Moler (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Monte Carlo (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Monte Carlo - PDE Problems (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Monte Carlo - Wasow (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Moore, Raymond (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Morgana (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Movies (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - NAS - Annapolis Cont (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - NASA (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - National Bureau of Standards - Division 11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NBS - Div 11 - Folder 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NAS - National Research Council (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Navigation, Opt (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Network (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Nevada (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Noise and Time Series (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Novosibirsk (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NSF - Education Project (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - NSF - Education (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NSF - Notes (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Number Theory (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Numerical Analysis - Basic Ideas (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Numerical Analysis - Curricula (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Numerical Analysis - Definition (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Numerical Analysis - Funds (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Numerical Analysis - Research - NSF (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Numerical Analysis - Seminar (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Numerical Analysis - Seminar (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Numerical Analysis - Seminar, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Numerical Analysis - Seminar, Winter 1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Numerical Analysis - Seminar, Autumn 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Numerical Analysis - Stanford Problems (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Numerical Analysis - SWAP (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Numerische Mathematik (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ODE - Problems (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ODE - Theory (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - O'Flaherty, Michael (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ONR - Advisory Committee (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - ONR Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - ONR Numerical Analysis Contract - Personnel (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - ONR Numerical Analysis Contract (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - ONR Research Advisory Group (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - ONR - NAC - Staff Group (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - ONR - NA - Proposals (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ordinary Differential Equations (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Ortega (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Orthogonal Polynomial (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - PACE (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto - Computer (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Parlett (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Parital Differential Equations (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - PDE - L-shaped Region (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - PDE - Book 24 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - PDE - Book ( Finite Difference Methods for PDE's GEF-Wasow) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - PDE - Book Corrections (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - PDE - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - PDE - Conj - 2 DIM (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - PDE - Conj - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - PDE - Conj ellipse (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - PDE - Conj higher lambda (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - PDE - Conj Polya (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - PDE - Conj - 1 DIM (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - PDE - Detached Shock (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - PDE - Difference Equations (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - PDE - Discretization Error (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - PDE - Flame - Richardson (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - PDE - Finite conj (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - PDE - lambda 2h less than lambda h (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - PDE - Madison (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - PDE - Network Analyzer (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - PDE - Princeton Ideas (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - PDE - Problems (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - PDE - Research Problems (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - PDE - SPADE (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - PDE - Young Theory (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Patterson (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Pavkovich (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Personal Contacts (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Personal - GEF (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Personnel (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Ph. D. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Ph. D. (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Ph. D. Persons - NA (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ph. D. NA Quals (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Ph. D. - Quals (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Ph. D. - Old (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Ph. D. Quals - NA (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ph. D. Quals - CSD (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ph. D. Quals (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ph. D. - Thesis topics (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Phi Betta Kappa (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Philco (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Philosophy (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Physics (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Plann ng - CSD only (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PL / ACME (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - PL / I (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PL360 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Van der Poel (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Pohl (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Polya (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Problems, Elementary Programs (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Procedures (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Programming Languages (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Provost's Computer Committee (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Provost's Computing - Oakford (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Psychology (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Publicity (includes pictures of GEF and Big Game, 1961) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Publicity (cont) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Purdy, Gerry (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Publication Policy (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Puzzles and Problems (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Random Digits (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Random Digits - Rosser Method (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Random Roundoff (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Rap Sessions, etc. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - R.W. - Diary (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Reactors (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Refereeing and Reviewing (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Regression (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Reinders (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Reading lists (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Research Ideas (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Research - Aborted Papers (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Research Thoughts, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Research Ideas, 1967-8 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Research Methodology (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Research Seminar (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Research Problems, Machine, 239 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Research Problems (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Richman (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rigal (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Round-off (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rounding Errors (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Rubin (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Russian Material (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Russian Survey - Chicago (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Russian Translation (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ryder, B (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sabbatical, etc. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Satterthwaite (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Saunders, Michael (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Scientific Agenda (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Schade, Christy (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Semi -Groups (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Seminar Attendance (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Shortliffe, Ted (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - SIAM (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - SIAM Trustees (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Simulation (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - SIREV - forms (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - SIREV - forms (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - SIREV - Hanan and Kurzbay 09220G (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - SIREV - Joyce 07210A (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - SIREV - Babushe 07220 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - SIREV - Cornille 01191E (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - SIREV - Boullion 02231G (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - SIREV - Ikebe 03251C (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - SIREV - Wasserstrom 05271D (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - SIREV - Kincaid 06171 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SIREV - Gregory 08121 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SIREV - Bass 12010H (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Security (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SLAC (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Roberta and Lyle (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SMSG (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SMSG - Computing (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Snow (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Social Implications of Computing (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Social Science Problems (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - SPADE (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Special Functions (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Spectrum Analysis (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - SPIRES (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Splines (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Spline Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Computation Center - Diary of Memorandums (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Statistics (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Stochastic Processes (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Stochastic Processes - Feller Lectures (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Stone, Mrs. Betty (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Stoutemyer, D. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Student Languages (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Student Unrest (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Summability (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Summability of Random Variables (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Swarthmore (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Symbol Manipulation (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Symposium (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Systems Programs (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - System / 360 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - System / 360 Floating Point (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Teaching Assistants (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Telegrapher's Equation (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Telegrapher's Delta - Equation (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Terman (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Time Sharing and Remote Stations (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Travel (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Travel Atlantic City, May 1972 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Travel Los Alamos, June 1972 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Travel Philadelphia, June 1972 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Travel Austin, Oct 1972 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Tennis (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Time (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - UCLA (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Underwood (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Varah (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Visitors (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Wirth (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Wilkinson (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Winograd (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Writing and Editing (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Carbon copies of GEF's outgoing correspondence
    - April - June 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jan-Mar 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Oct-Dec 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Jul-Sep 1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - April - June 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Jan-Mar 1970 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Oct-Dec 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Jul-Sep 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - April - June 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Jan-Mar 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Oct-Dec 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Jul-Oct 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - April - July 1968 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Jan-Apr 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Nov 1967-Jan 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Sep-Nov 1967 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Jan-Sep 1967 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Jun-Dec 1966 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - May 1966 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - March - April 1966 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Jan-Feb 1966 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Nov-Dec 1965 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Sep-Oct 1965 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - July - August 1965 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - May - June 1965 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - March - April 1965 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Jan-Feb 1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Nov-Dec 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Sep-Oct 1964 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Jul-Aug 1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - May - June 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - March - April 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Jan-Feb 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - GEF's desk calendars, 1960 - 1972 (Box 15, Folder nf)
  - Notes from classes (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Notes from Math 203 N.Y.U., Fall 1955-6
    - Notes from J.D.Tamarkin's Math 227-8, Fourier Series, 1939-40
    - Notes from J.D. Tamarkin's Math 237-8, Probability (taken by GEF and Jack Herriot), 1938-9
    - Notes from D.W. Hall's Topology I, Brown, 1939-40
  - Index to GEF's publications (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - II (B1-B20) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - A-1 lectures - III (B21-B40) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - II (cont) (B41-58) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Determination of Absolute Height and Wind for Aircraft Operations (C1) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Aircraft Weather Reconnaissance (C3) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Russian Math Monographs (C4), 1930-1951 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - IV (C2-D7) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - D3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - D3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - D4 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - V (E1-E56) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - VI (F0-F43) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - VI (cont) (F43-F80) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - VI-A (F81-F100) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - VI-A (cont) (F101-122) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - VI-B (F123-F130) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - VI-B (cont) (F131-F140) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - VI-B (cont) (F141-G10) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Ph. D. Thesis - Summability of Random Variables (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Math 136, Summer 1954 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Linear Algebra Notes, Spring 1961 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Math 136, Autumn 1961 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - CS136, Autumn 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - CS136, Winter 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - CS137 Computer Problems (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - CS138, Spring 1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - CS137, Winter 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - CS126, Spring 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - CS136, Summer 1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - CS5, Autumn 1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - CS237b, Winter 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - CS5, Autumn 1965 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - CS136, Winter 1966 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - CS5, Spring 1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - CS204, Autumn 1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - CS136, Winter 1968 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - CS138, Spring 1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - CS136, Autumn 1963-9 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - CS237c, Spring 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - CS126, Winter 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CS50a, Spring 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Math 237 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Math 237 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Class Notes (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SWAC-1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - SWAC-2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Four volume set of unidentified notes, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder nf)
  - Four Stanford class roll books, 1957-61 (Box 18, Folder nf)
  - Original Index to GEF's personal professional files (Box 18, Folder nf)
  - Assorted Computer Printouts (Box 19)
  - Card File-Matrix Bibliography, (2 drawers) (Box 19)
  - Assorted Computer Printouts (Box 20)
  - Administration and Correspondence at Stanford (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Appoinments and Salaries at Stanford (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Karl Karlstrom (Prentic-Hall Publishers) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between George Forsyth and Prentice-Hall Inventory of locations purchasing Book Reviews (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Offers of teching positions and directorships at various universities (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Material concerning the George Forsythe Lectures and Awards in Computer Science (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Material concerning George Forsythe's Death; Miscellaneous Computer Material (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with U.C.L.A. and National Bureau of Standards (contracts) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Abstracts and Lectures (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Day Programming Race (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Problems on "Tic Tac Toe" (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Diaries (daybooks):, 1960-1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Alexandra Forsythe Papers, 1970-1979; Series 2
  - Paper by W. Kahan and B.N. Parlett (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Secondary Careers for Women" material (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Computer Forum (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vacation around the world material (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tuscon, Arizona vacation (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Circle Z Ranch" vacation (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Material on Hawaii (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Exams from Computer Science Course at Gunn High School (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Material from Detroit, Mich., Insititute of Technology (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Math. Problems (High School) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Math Problems (High School) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Material for lecture to be given at National Teachers Conference (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Test Keys from Gunn Computer Science Class, Student Programs (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Material from Computer Science 105 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Co-Authors, Friends and Stanford (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Computer Education in High Schools (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Authors (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Book Lists (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Vacation Material, Symposiums and Wisconsin Conference Material (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gunn High School Computer Science Material, Tests and Computer Runs, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gunn High School Computer Science Course Material (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gunn HIgh School Computer Science Material, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Material from Computer Aided Geometric Design Conference; Pricelists from Computer Companies (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Course Material from lectures on Flow Charts (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between atuhors and publishers (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Copies of contract with Prentice-Hall Publishers (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Reviews and letter from publishers (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Authors/PUblishers (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Book reviews for Mathematics Teacher and American Science (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Authors/Publishers; Author Questionnaire (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Authors/Publishers (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Contracts for Cubberley and Gunn High Schools; Teacher Evaluations; Grades (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Course Evaluations (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Burroughs Co. and A. Forsythe (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Authors/ Publishers (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - International Research Conference at Los Alamos New Mexico (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Co-Authors; Letters from John Wiley Publishing Co. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between co-authors and publishers; Various book reviews (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Stanford University (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - First Draft of Text; Exams for Computer Science Courses; List of Forsythe Publications (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gunn High School Involvement with Stanford Computer Network (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Suggested program for gifted H.S. Students in Math. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Letters RE: G. Forsythes Death (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Letters RE: G. Forstyhe's Death (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Nixon Elementary School Discovery Group Material (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Additional Papers, Series 3
  - School Mathematics Study Group. Algorithms Computation and Mathematics. Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University, Student text and teachter's commentary, 1965; (2 v.) (Box 1)
  - School Mathematics Study Group. Algorithms Computation and Mathematics.. (Algol Supplement). Student text and teacher's commentary, (2 v.) (Box 1)
  - School Mathematics Study Group. Algorithms Computation and Mathematics.. (Fortran Supplement). Student text and teacher's commentary, (2 v.) (Box 1)
  - Forsythe, George. Computer Solution of Linear Algebraic Systems. In Russian (Box 1)
  - Forsythe, George. Computer Methods for Mathematical Computations. In Japanese (Box 1)
  - Forsythe, Alexandra. Computer Science: BASIC Language Programming. In Japanese. (Box 1)
  - Forsythe, Alexandra. Computer Science, A First Course. In Spanish, Portuguese, Japanese. (Box 2)
  - Forsythe, Alexandra. Computer Science: BASIC Language Programming. In Spanish (Box 2)
  - Forsythe, Alexandra. Computer Science: FORTRAN Language Programming. In Spanish and Dutch (Box 2)
  - Forsythe, Alexandra. Computer Science - Projects and Study Problems. In Spanish. (Box 2)
  - Lindsay, Robert Bruce and Henry Margenau, Foundations of Physics; New York: John Wiley & Sons, with annotations by George Forsythe, 1936 (Box 3, Folder nf)
  - Forsythe, George. "Notes for Seminar on Computational Aspects of Linear Problems (Mathematics 251)"; Dept. of Mathematics, UCIA, mimeographed notebook, 1956 (Box 3, Folder nf)
  - Bibliography on numerical solution of elliptic partial differential equations, 1972; (printout of J734.PDE) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Computer Science and Mathematics," revised remarks from a panel for mathematicians sponsored by the Conference Board of the Mathematical Sciences at San Antonio, TX, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Index to subroutines and programs, 1971; (printout of TOOO.MATHSUBJECTINDEX) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memo on computing in Australia and New Zealand, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified printout (Box 3, Folder 5)
General note
COMMON ABBREVIATIONS USED IN THIS COLLECTION
AAAS American Association for the Advancement of Science
AAUP American Association of University Professors
ACM Association for Computing Machinery
ARPA Advance Research Projects Agency
CS Computer Science (Forsythe's)
CS137 137 is class number (Forsythe's)
CSD Computer Science Department (Forsythe's)
COSINE Committee on Computer Science in Electrical Engineering
COSRIMS Committee on Support of Research in Mathematical Sciences
CUPM Committee on the Undergraduate Program in Mathematics
FJCC Fall Joint Computer Conference
IEEE Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineering
IFIP International Federation for Information Processing
NA Numerical Analysis (Forsythe's)
NAS National Academy of Sciences
NBS National Bureau of Standards
NDEA National Defense Education Act
NSF National Science Foundation
ODE Ordinary Differential Equations (Forsythe's)
ONR Office of Naval Research
PDE Partial Differential Equations (Forsythe's)
SICCSE Special Interest Committee on Computer Science Education
SIAM Society of Industrial and Applied Mathematics
SIGNUM Special Interest Group on Numerical Mathematics
SIREV SIAM Review
SLAC Stanford Linear Accellerator Center
SMSG School Mathematics Study Group
SPADE Subcommittee On Partial Differential Equations
SPIRES Stanford Physics Information Retrieval System
SWAC NBS Western Automatic Computer
PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES MENTIONED
ALGOL
ALGOL W
BALGOL
COBOL
FORTRAN
PL/ACME
PL/I
PL/360